Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/nguyentam-6a9b15226 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Git

JavaScript

Amazon Web Services (AWS)

Nguyen Tam

Software Engineer

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

Software engineer with experience in Fullstack Development. My focus is on bringing value through my work and ensuring that every project I undertake is a success. With the goal of becoming an expert in software development and eventually a team leader, I am committed to expanding my knowledge and expertise in the field.

Skills:

Framework: NodeJS/Express/NestJS/ReactJS Language: TypeScript/JavaScript, HTML/CSS

Database: MongoDB, Redis, SQL

English: IETLS 7.0 Currently learning: Go

Experience

OPSWAT

Software Engineer October 2023 - Present (1 year 6 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

CMC Global Company Limited. Software Engineer September 2022 - September 2023 (1 year 1 month)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

TMA Solutions Back End Developer January 2021 - July 2022 (1 year 7 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Bosch Vietnam Intern March 2020 - September 2020 (7 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Education

Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology

Bachelor's degree, Electrical and Electronics Engineering · (September 2017 - April 2022)